A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.39 (A2014) FA760
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2014.003: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2001-2014; AC_2014_003; 31.44 Cubic Feet 24 standard record storage boxes, R4389-R4412
  - THS, 2007-2013; AC_2014_003_3; 9.2 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - 2009 THS 345 - INTERNATIONAL FINANCE CORPORATION - HEALTH IN AFRICA INITIATIVE, 2009-2012 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 346 - MEDICAL EDUCATION COOPERATION WITH CUBA - SPECIAL ISSUES OF "MEDICC REVIEW" JOURNAL, 2009-2011 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 347 - INTERNATIONAL BANK FOR RECONSTRUCTION AND DEVELOPMENT - FLAGSHIP PROGRAM ON HEALTH SYSTEMS STRENGTHENING, 2009-2012 (Box R4396)
      Scope and Contents
      Grant was voided
    - 2009 THS 348 - INTERNATIONAL AIDS SOCIETY (SWITZERLAND) - MEETING ON HIV PROGRAMMES AND HEALTH SYSTEMS STRENGTHENING, 2009-2010 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 349 - PROJECT HOPE - HEALTH AFFAIRS JOURNAL: PUBLICATION OF THE BELLAGIO 08 eHEALTH PAPERS, 2009-2010 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 350 - AMERICAN MEDICAL INFORMATICS ASSOCIATION - HEALTH INFORMATICS BUILDING BLOCKS PROGRAM, 2009-2011 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 353 - CORPORATE COUNCIL ON AFRICA - HEALTH INSURANCE AND PRIVATE SECTOR PANELS AT BIENNIAL CONFERENCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 354 - MCKINSEY COMPANY - TRANSITION COST OF HEALTH SYSTEM REFORM TOWARDS UNIVERSAL COVERAGE, 2009-2010 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 354 - Catalyzing Change - The System Reform Costs of Universal Health Coverage - Published Materials, 2009-2010; 2014:003:035 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 357 - HASELTINE FOUNDATION FOR MEDICAL SCIENCES AND THE ARTS - HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS IN SOUTH ASIA, 2009-2012 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 THS 358 - BROADREACH HEALTHCARE - HEALTH MARKET RESEARCH ACTIVITIES IN SOUTH AFRICA, 2009-2012 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 THS 360 - UNITED STATES FUND FOR UNICEF - MATERNAL AND CHILD SOCIAL HEALTH INSURANCE SURVEY, 2009-2012 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 THS 361 - UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO (CANADA) - CANADA'S STRATEGIC ROLE IN GLOBAL HEALTH, 2009-2011 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 THS 362 - GLOBAL FORUM FOR HEALTH RESEARCH (SWITZERLAND) - INNOVATING FOR THE HEALTH OF ALL CONFERENCE IN HAVANA, CUBA, 2009-2012 (Box R4397)
    - 2010 THS 301 - AFRICAN CENTER FOR ECONOMIC TRANSFORMATION - GHANA UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE ACTIVITIES, 2010-2011 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 302 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - HEALTH SYSTEMS AND RELATED ACTIVITIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 303 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN FRANCISCO - iHEA 8TH WORLD CONGRESS ON HEALTH ECONOMICS, 2009-2011 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 304 - HEARTFILE (PAKISTAN) - PEER REVIEW MEETING OF THE PAKISTAN LANCET SERIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 305 - SAHIA ASSOCIATION (SOUTH AFRICA) - 13TH WORLD CONGRESS ON MEDICAL AND HEALTH INFORMATICS, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 306 - CEDAR ASSOCIATES - ASSESSING COVERAGE DECISIONS IN LOW-AND MIDDLE-INCOME COUNTRIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 307 - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ASIAN RESEARCH - 2010 PACIFIC HEALTH SUMMIT, 2010-2011 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 309 - GLOBAL HEALTHCARE INFORMATION NETWORK (UNITED KINGDOM) - HEALTH INFORMATION FOR ALL BY 2015, 2010-2011 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 310 - UNIVERSITY FOR DEVELOPMENT, CHILE - UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 313 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - eHEALTH MONOGRAPH SERIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 314 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH POLICY PROGRAM (THAILAND) - 5TH ASIA-PACIFIC ACTION ALLIANCE ON HUMAN RESOURCES FOR HEALTH CONFERENCE, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 315 - AFRICAN HEALTH ECONOMICS AND POLICY ASSOCIATION (UNITED KINGDOM) - BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT CAPACITY BUILDING, 2010-2011 (Box R4412)
    - 2010 THS 316 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH, BANGLADESH - INDIA AND THAILAND AND UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE, 2010-2011 (Box R4412)
  - TRA, 2008-2011; AC_2014_003_4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 TRA 301 - COUNCIL ON FOUNDATIONS - METROPOLITAN POLICY CONVENING FOR PHILANTHROPIC ORGANIZATIONS, 2008-2009 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 302 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - REPORT ON HOUSING AND TRANSPORTATION, 2008-2009 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA302 - Retooling HUD for a Catalytic Federal Government: A Report to Secretary Shaun Donovan - Published Material, 2008-2009; 2014:003:037 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 303 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - CONGRESSIONAL PROGRAM ON CLIMATE AND ENERGY SECURITY, 2008-2010 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA303 - Energy Security and Climate Change - Policy Challenges for the New Administration and the New Congress - Published Material, 2008-2010; 2014:003:036 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 305 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - CONFERENCE, TRANSFORMING THE TRANSPORTATION SECTOR (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 306 - REGIONAL PLAN ASSOCIATION - PLANNING AND DEVELOPING TRANSPORTATION VISUALIZATION TOOLS, 2009-2010 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 307 - SECURING AMERICA'S FUTURE ENERGY FOUNDATION - TRANSPORTATION REFORM (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 311 - CENTER FOR PUBLIC INTEGRITY - INVESTIGATIVE REPORTS ON LOBBYING INFLUENCES AND TRANSPORTATION POLICY, 2009-2010 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 313 - URBAN HABITAT PROGRAM - TRANSPORTATION, LAND-USE, AND CLIMATE EQUITY POLICIES, 2009-2011 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 316 - UNITED STATES PUBLIC INTEREST RESEARCH GROUP EDUCATION FUND - NEW TRANSPORTATION FUTURE CAMPAIGN, 2008-2011 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 319 - NAACP LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - EQUITY ADVOCACY, 2009-2011 (Box R4397)
    - 2009 TRA 323 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - CLIMATE AND TRANSPORTATION - POLICY ANALYSIS CENTER, 2009-2011 (Box R4397)
  - Agriculture (AGR), 2010-2012; AC_2014_003_5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 AGR 301 - REGIONAL UNIVERSITIES FORUM FOR CAPACITY BUILDING IN AGRICULTURE (UGANDA) - PLANNING MEETING ON AGRICULTURAL TRAINING NEEDS IN AFRICA, 2010-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 AGR 302 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - INITIATIVE ON FOOD AND AGRICULTURE POLICY, 2010-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 AGR 303 - PAMOJA MEDIA EAST AFRICA LIMITED (KENYA) - ONLINE AND MOBILE SOCIAL NETWORKING PLATFORM, 2010-2012 (Box R4398)
  - Campaign for American Workers (CAW), 2006-2013; AC_2014_003_6; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 CAW 301 - BOSTON COLLEGE - WITHHOLDING-TO-DEBT-REDUCTION PILOT PROGRAM, 2009-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 303 - LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT RELATIONS ASSOCIATION - EMPLOYMENT POLICY RESEARCH NETWORK, 2010-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 304 - PARTNERSHIP FOR WORKING FAMILIES - CONSTRUCTION CAREERS PROGRAM, 2010-2012 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 306 - AARP - STRENGTHENING SOCIAL SECURITY RELATED ACTIVITIES, 2009-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 307 - FREEDMAN CONSULTING, LLC - POLICY-RELATED CONSULTATION TO SELECTED CAW GRANTEES, 2008-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 308 - CENTER FOR AMERICAN PROGRESS - SOCIAL SECURITY CARES, 2010-2012 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 309 - NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT LAW PROJECT - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE SAFETY NET PROJECT, 2008-2012 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 312 - GRANTMAKERS IN HEALTH - NATIONAL HEALTH REFORM IMPLEMENTATION STRATEGY, 2010-2011 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 313 - NATIONAL PARTNERSHIP FOR WOMEN AND FAMILIES - PAID FAMILY LEAVE INITIATIVE, 2010-2012 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 314 - NEW AMERICA FOUNDATION - "NEXT SOCIAL CONTRACT" INITIATIVE, 2006-2012 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 315 - NATIONAL WOMEN'S LAW CENTER - PROMOTING THE ECONOMIC SECURITY OF WOMEN, 2010-2012 (Box R4398)
    - 2010 CAW 316 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - RETIREMENT POLICY FOR AMERICAN WORKERS, 2010-2013 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 317 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - "SECURING THE SAFETY OF RETIREMENT SAVINGS" PROJECT, 2009-2013 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 318 - EARNED ASSET RESOURCE NETWORK - SAVER'S TAX CREDIT, 2010-2012 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 319 - D2D FUND - PROMOTE SAVINGS BONDS, 2007-2012 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 320 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - RF POLICY IMPACT FORUM, 2009-2013 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 321 - NEW AMERICA FOUNDATION - PAYROLL DEDUCTION SAVINGS PROGRAM, 2007-2012 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 322 - COMMUNITY CATALYST, INC. - AFFORDABLE CARE ACT IMPLEMENTATION FUND, 2010-2012 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CAW 323 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - HEALTH CARE AND RETIREMENT SECURITY COUNSELING, 2007-2013 (Box R4399)
  - CIF, 2010-2014; AC_2014_003_7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 CIF 302 - DEMOS: A NETWORK FOR IDEAS AND ACTION, LTD. - ARTS AND CULTURE AND URBAN COMMUNITIES, 2010-2011 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CIF 303 - EMCARTS INC. - NEW YORK - NEW PATHWAYS FOR THE ARTS PROGRAM, 2010-2012 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CIF 304 - 3-LEGGED DOG - NEW WORKS OF EXPERIMENTAL PERFORMING ART, 2010-2013 (Box R4399)
    - 2010 CIF 306 - NEW YORK HALL OF SCIENCE - REGENERATION - ART, TECHNOLOGY AND SCIENCE BIENNIAL, 2010-2013 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 308 - DANCE THEATRE OF HARLEM - NEW DANCE WORKS, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 309 - EXIT ART/THE FIRST WORLD - "DIGIMOVIES" THEATER, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 310 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - SEASON OF CAMBODIA ARTS FESTIVAL, 2010-2013 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 311 - SEVENTH REGIMENT ARMORY CONSERVANCY - DANCE PRESENTATIONS, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 312 - PRATT INSTITUTE - INTEGRATE THE ARTS INTO SUSTAINABLE NEIGHBORHOODS INITIATIVE, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 313 - RESEARCH FOUNDATION OF THE CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - NEW YORK CITY DIGITAL ENVIRONMENTAL ATLAS, 2010-2013 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 314 - QUEENS MUSEUM OF ART - SOCIAL PRACTICE MASTERS OF FINE ARTS PROGRAM, CORONA STUDIO, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 315 - FOUNDRY THEATRE - ARTISTIC WORKS EXPLORING NEW YORK CITY LIFE, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 316 - BOWERY ARTS AND SCIENCE - POETRY PRESENTATION, A WHITE WING BRUSHING THE BUILDING, 2010-2014 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 317 - RANDALL'S ISLAND SPORTS FOUNDATION - ENVIRONMENTAL SCULPTURE AND MUSIC INSTALLATION, 2011-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 318 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY AFRICAN DIASPORAN ARTS - "SOUL OF BROOKLYN" CONSORTIUM, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 319 - HOSTOS COMMUNITY COLLEGE FOUNDATION - "THE YOUNG ROOTS SERIES: INNOVATION OUT OF TRADITION", 2010-2013 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 319 - The Mermaid's Feet Catarina dos Santos Raquel Rivera - Digital, 2010-2013; 2014:003:030 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 319 - Los Monstritos New Wave Percussion - Digital, 2010-2013; 2014:003:031 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 319 - Batey y Mscorix: Senderos de Carbon Sita Frederick - Digital, 2010-2013; 2014:003:032 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF 319 - De Rumbo de Rumba Noemi Segarra/Henry Cole - Digital, 2010-2013; 2014:003:033 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CIF319 - Non-Demonizational Nation La Bruja - Digital, 2010-2013; 2014:003:034 (Box R4400)
  - Clitmate Change (CLI), 2008-2013; AC_2014_003_8; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 CLI 301 - INSTITUTE OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES OF RWANDA - STRENGTHENING CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION FOR AGRICULTURE, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CLI 303 - SOKOINE UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE (TANZANIA) - BUILDING CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION IN THE AGRICULTURAL SECTOR, 2010-2013 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CLI 307 - REGIONAL UNIVERSITIES FORUM FOR CAPACITY BUILDING IN AGRICULTURE (UGANDA) - CLIMATE CHANGE FUNDING TRAINING OPPORTUNITIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4400)
    - 2010 CLI 309 - WORLD FOOD PROGRAMME (ITALY) - RETHINKING INTERNATIONAL DISASTER AID FINANCE, 2008-2012 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 311 - UNITED NATIONS ECONOMIC COMMISSION FOR AFRICA (ETHIOPIA) - SEVENTH AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT FORUM ON CLIMATE CHANGE, 2010-2011 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 319 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT (ENGLAND) - URBAN ADAPTATION TO CLIMATE CHANGE IN SUPPORT OF THE IPCC'S FIFTH ASSESSMENT, 2010-2012 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 320 - NATIONAL RELIGIOUS PARTNERSHIP FOR THE ENVIRONMENT - INTERNATIONAL ADAPTATION FUNDING MEETING, 2010-2011 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 321 - RESOURCE INNOVATION GROUP - CLIMATE PREPAREDNESS LEARNING ADAPTATION NETWORK, 2010-2011 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 322 - FEDERAL EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT AGENCY - COMMUNITY RESILIENCE INNOVATION CHALLENGE AWARDS, 2010-2013 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 324 - INSTITUTE FOR SOCIAL AND ENVIRONMENTAL TRANSITION - STORM RESISTANT HOUSING LIVELIHOOD DEVELOPMENT FOR WOMEN IN DA NANG CITY, VIETNAM, 2010-2011 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 327 - MERCY CORPS - SEMARANG, INDONESIA- PRE-FEASIBILITY STUDY OF RAINWATER HARVESTING SYSTEMS, 2010-2012 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CLI 329 - MERCY CORPS - BANDAR LAMPUNG, INDONESIA INTEGRATED SOLID WASTE MANAGEMENT MASTER PLAN, 2010-2012 (Box R4401)
  - CPR, 2008-2013; AC_2014_003_9; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 CPR 201 - WILLIAM J. CLINTON FOUNDATION - CARBON AND POVERTY REDUCTION PARTNERSHIP (1 and 1 SUPPL), 2008-2013 (Box R4401)
    - 2010 CPR 202 - CARE USA - CARBON CREDITS FOR CROP PRODUCTION IN KENYA, 2010-2013 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 CPR 204 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - GLOBAL DIALOGUE ON AGRICULTURE AND CLIMATE CHANGE, 2010-2011 (Box R4402)
  - DSN, 2008-2013; AC_2014_003_11; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 DSN 301 - GRADUATE INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL AND DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (SWITZERLAND) - BELLAGIO CONFERENCES ON GLOBAL HEALTH DIPLOMACY, 2009-2013 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 DSN 302 - NUCLEAR THREAT INITIATIVE - GLOBAL COLLABORATION IN DISEASE SURVEILLANCE, 2008-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 DSN 305 - MCGILL UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - BC CONFERENCE: ON GLOBAL HEALTH DIPLOMACY, 2010-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 DSN 307 - CHIANG MAI UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - ONE HEALTH LEADERSHIP MEETING (Box R4402)
    - 2010 DSN 308 - SWISS TROPICAL AND PUBLIC HEALTH INSTITUTE - EVALUATION OF THE DSN AFRICA PROGRAM INITIATIVE, 2010-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 DSN 312 - CARLETON UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - GLOBAL HEALTH DIPLOMACY NETWORK, 2009-2013 (Box R4402)
  - EIN, 2009-2013; AC_2014_003_12; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 EIN 301 - BELLWETHER EDUCATION PARTNERS - MARKET INVOLVEMENT IN THE U.S. PUBLIC SECTOR, 2010-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 EIN 302 - PARTNERSHIP FOR PUBLIC SERVICE - INNOVATION IN FEDERAL GOVERNMENT, 2009-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 EIN 303 - PUBLIC ALLIES - PILOTING COMMUNITY INNOVATION PROJECT, 2010-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 EIN 305 - MAYOR'S FUND TO ADVANCE NEW YORK CITY - NETWORKED GOVERNANCE PROJECT, 2010-2013 (Box R4402)
  - EVA, 2009-2012; AC_2014_003_13; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 EVA 302 - CENTER FOR EFFECTIVE PHILANTHROPY - GRANTEE PERCEPTION REPORT, 2010-2011 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 EVA 306 - GLOBALGIVING FOUNDATION - MONITORING AND EVALUATION PROJECT, 2009-2012 (Box R4402)
    - 2010 EVA 307 - ROYAL MELBOURNE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (AUSTRALIA) - EVALADVISOR PROJECT, 2009-2012 (Box R4403)
  - Innovation (INN), 2007-2013; AC_2014_003_14; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 INN 301 - YOUNG FOUNDATION (UNITED KINGDOM) - SOCIAL INNOVATION EXCHANGE AND INNOVATION ACADEMY, 2010-2011 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INN 302 - ASHOKA - CHANGEMAKERS INITIATIVE, 2007-2013 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INN 303 - MAKER FAIRE AFRICA (NETHERLANDS) - 2011 AND 2012 SHOWCASE INNOVATIONS ORIGINATING IN AFRICA, 2010-2013 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INN 304 - NETHOPE - INNOVATION FOR DEVELOPMENT OFFICE, 2010-2011 (Box R4403)
  - INV, 2005-2013; AC_2014_003_15; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2010 INV 303 - BRIDGES VENTURES (UNITED KINGDOM) - "INVESTING FOR IMPACT" REPORT (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 305 - MICROFINANCE INFORMATION EXCHANGE - DATA-SHARING PLATFORM FOR IMPACT INVESTING, 2010-2011 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 306 - SHARED INTEREST - ADVISORY SERVICES ON A CAPITAL RAISING IN SOUTH AFRICA, 2010-2011 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 307 - CALVERT FOUNDATION - ENTERPRISE INNOVATION FUND SYMPOSIUM, 2010-2011 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 309 - INTELLECAP INC. - SANKALP SOCIAL ENTERPRISE FORUMS, 2010-2012 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 310 - NEIGHBORHOOD FUNDERS GROUP - PROGRAM-RELATED INVESTMENT (PRI) MAKERS NETWORK, 2005-2012 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 312 - CERES - WATER AND SUSTAINABILITY FRAMEWORK, 2010-2012 (Box R4403)
    - 2010 INV 313 - GROWTH PHILANTHROPY NETWORK - SOCIAL IMPACT EXCHANGE INITIATIVE, 2010-2012 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 314 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP LP - MARKET-BASED SOLUTIONS TO POVERTY IN AFRICA, 2010-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 314 - Promise and Progress - Market-Based Solutions on Poverty in Africa - Published Material, 2010-2011; 2014:003:041 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 315 - UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA (SOUTH AFRICA) - CHINESE STAKEHOLDERS EDUCATION ON RESPONSIBLE INVESTING IN AFRICA (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 315 - Promoting the Concept of Impact Investing in the Social and Environmental Space for Chinese Investors in Africa - Published Material, 2014:003:040 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 315 - Gordon Institute of Business Science: University of Pretoria, Promoting Impact Investing from China into Africa - Digial, 2014:003:042-2014:003:045 (Box R4404)
    - Promoting the Concept of Impact Investing in the Social and Environmental Space for Chinese Investor in Africa - Digital, 2010; 2014:003:046, 2014:003:047 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 315 - Promoting the Concept of Impact Investing in the Social and Environmental Space for Chinese Investors in Africa - Part 1 2 - Digital, 2014:003:062, 2014:003:063 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 315 - Promoting the Concept of Impact Investing in the Social and Environmental Space for Chinese Investors in Africa - Ghana - Digital, 2014:003:061 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV315 - Promoting the Concept of Impact Investing in the Social and Environmental Space for Chinese Investors in Africa - Digital, 2014:003:059, 2014:003:060 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 317 - SOCIAL INVESTMENT FORUM FOUNDATION - 2009-10 EDITION OF THE TRENDS REPORT, 2010-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 317 - 2010 Report on Socially Responsible Investing Trends in the United States - Published Material, 2010-2011; 2014:003:039 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 319 - LION'S HEAD GLOBAL PARTNERS (UNITED KINGDOM) -AFRICAN AGRICULTURE IMPACT INVESTING PRINCIPLES, 2010-2012 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 320 - GOLDMARK PRODUCTIONS - BRINGING IMPACT INVESTING TO THE MAINSTREAM MEDIA, 2010-2012 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 322 - FINANCIAL TIMES (ENGLAND) - RESEARCH ON IMPACT INVESTING IN AFRICA, 2010-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 322 - This is Africa: A Global Perspective Special Report COP17 - Published Material, 2010-2011; 2014:003:038 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 323 - PENNSYLVANIA TREASURY DEPARTMENT - ENERGY-EFFICIENCY FINANCING MODELS, 2010-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 324 - CALVERT FOUNDATION - IMPACT INVESTMENT VEHICLES, 2010-2012 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 325 - DALBERG CONSULTING (SOUTH AFRICA) - ASSESSMENT OF IMPACT INVESTMENT IN WEST AFRICA, 2010-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 326 - GRAMEEN FOUNDATION USA - SOLUTIONS FOR THE POOREST IN INDIA, 2010-2013 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 327 - GREATER CINCINNATI FOUNDATION - DEVELOP AN IMPACT INVESTING DONOR ADVISED FUND, 2010-2012 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 328 - B LAB - B CORPORATIONS PROJECT, 2007-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 332 - ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY PARTNERS - COMMUNITY IMPACT INVESTING PROJECT, 2010-2011 (Box R4404)
    - 2010 INV 333 - AGORA PARTNERSHIPS - ACCELERATOR INITIATIVE IN CENTRAL AMERICA, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 INV 334 - EVERGREEN COOPERATIVE DEVELOPMENT FUND - GREEN JOBS OHIO INVESTMENT FUND, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 INV 336 - SMALL ENTERPRISE EDUCATION AND PROMOTION NETWORK - SOCIAL PERFORMANCE WORKING GROUP, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 INV 337 - FINANCIAL SECTOR DEEPENING TRUST (TANZANIA) - AGRICULTURAL FINANCE MARKETS, 2010-2013 (Box R4405)
  - JAC, 2010-2012; AC_2014_003_16; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 JAC 302 - ISLAND PRESS - IDEAS THAT MATTER PUBLICATION, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
  - MKT, 2010-2012; AC_2014_003_17; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 MKT 301 - ALLIANCE FOR A GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA (KENYA) - MARKET ACCESS PROGRAM, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
  - OAF, 2010-2013; AC_2014_003_18; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 OAF 301 - WILTON PARK (ENGLAND) - CONFERENCE, AFRICA 2010 - THE KEY CHALLENGES (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAF 302 - GSMA FOUNDATION - BOOK ON THE IMPACT OF MOBILE BANKING IN KENYA, 2010-2013 (Box R4405)
  - OPP, 2003-2013; AC_2014_003_19; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 OPP 301 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - 13TH ANNUAL DINKINS FORUM (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 302 - NEW MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - FESTIVAL OF IDEAS FOR A NEW CITY, 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 303 - MUSEUM OF ARTS AND DESIGN - EXHIBITION, "THE GLOBAL AFRICA PROJECT", 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 304 - MAYOR'S FUND TO ADVANCE NEW YORK CITY - "URBAN CANVAS DESIGN COMPETITION" (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 305 - NEW YORK LANDMARKS CONSERVANCY - TECHNICAL SERVICES PROGRAM, 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 306 - ASIA SOCIETY - NINE LIVES - IN SEARCH OF THE SACRED IN MODERN INDIA, 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 307 - CENTER FOR NEW YORK CITY NEIGHBORHOODS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 308 - EL BARRIO'S OPERATION FIGHTBACK - DEVELOPMENT OF PS109 IN EAST HARLEM (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OPP 309 - CITY FUTURES - STRENGTHEN NEW YORK CITY'S CREATIVE SECTOR, 2009-2011 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 310 - HIP-HOP THEATER FESTIVAL, INC. - 10TH ANNUAL HIP-HOP THEATER FESTIVAL, 2003-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 311 - THE NEW SCHOOL - ARTS AND CULTURE IN NEW YORK CITY AND TORONTO, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 312 - CEOs FOR CITIES, NFP - "ONE MINUTE FOR YOUR CITY" CAMPAIGN, 2010-2011 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 313 - CITY PARKS ALLIANCE - INTERNATIONAL URBAN PARKS CONFERENCE, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 315 - PERFORMANCE ZONE - ECONOMIC REVITALIZATION FOR PERFORMING ARTISTS, 2007-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 316 - WILDCAT SERVICE CORPORATION - FORECLOSURE MITIGATION-TRANSITIONAL EMPLOYMENT PILOT, 2008-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 318 - ISAMU NOGUCHI FOUNDATION AND GARDEN MUSEUM - "STUDIES IN SPACE, ART AND CIVIC ACTION" PROJECT, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 319 - CITY FUTURES - NEW YORK CITY OPPORTUNITIES THOUGHT PAPERS AND COVENINGS, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 320 - SOLOMON R. GUGGENHEIM FOUNDATION - WALKING TOURS OF "STILL SPOTS" IN NEW YORK CITY, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 322 - URBAN WORD NYC - NEW YORK CITY YOUTH POET LAUREATE PROJECT, 2010-2013 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP322 - Clutch. - Published Material, 2010-2013; 2014:003:065 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 OPP 323 - MUSEUM OF MODERN ART - EXHIBITION AND WORKSHOP, "PALISADES BAY", 2009-2012 (Box R4406)
  - PHS, 2001-2012; AC_2014_003_21; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 PHS 301 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - PHILANTHROPY GROUP WORKSHOPS, 2009-2010 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 PHS 303 - WORLD AFFAIRS COUNCIL OF NORTHERN CALIFORNIA - GLOBAL PHILANTHROPY FORUM, 2009-2011 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 PHS 311 - KENYA COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION - AFRICAN GRANTMAKERS NETWORK CONFERENCE, 2010-2011 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 PHS 312 - FOUNDATION CENTER - GLOBAL DATA PLATFORM, 2010-2011 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 PHS 314 - THAI FUND FOUNDATION - CERTIFICATE COURSE ON RESOURCE MOBILIZATION FOR PHILANTHROPY, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 PHS 315 - POPULATION AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (THAILAND) - NEW GENERATION OF PHILANTHROPISTS, 2010-2012 (Box R4406)
    - 2010 PHS 316 - PHILANTHROPY NEW YORK - D5 INITIATIVE, 2001-2011 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PHS 317 - EAST AFRICA ASSOCIATION OF GRANTMAKERS (KENYA) - STATE AND NATURE OF PHILANTHROPY, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
  - PRD, 2010-2013; AC_2014_003_22; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 PRD 201 - CHILDLINE KENYA - CHILD ABUSE HOTLINE, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRD 202 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP LP - OUTSOURCING EMPLOYMENT IN INDIA AND KENYA, 2010-2011 (Box R4407)